# PEE JAY ESLAWAN

## INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

31-D Población, Davao City PH 8000 | +63 961 080 9958 | eslawanpeejay1@gmail.com

#### **SUMMARY**

Web and mobile developer with a background in building user-friendly applications. Experienced in developing both frontend and backend components using technologies such as **React Native**, **Expo**, **Node.js**, **Tailwind CSS**, and **SQL databases**. Knowledgeable in integrating **RESTful APIs**, implementing **JWT** authentication, and utilizing cloud platforms like **Google Cloud Services**, **AWS Amazon RDS**, and **Hostinger**.

#### **PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE**

## **DOLE XI | CAPSTONE PROJECT**

August 2024 - Present

 Developed a web and mobile property management system, integrated QR Code equipment tracking system and Data Analytics features providing actionable insights and enhancing decision-making capabilities.

## FinTech | Account Specialist

Sept 2022 - Nov 2023

 Managed international currency exchanges, bank transfers, and forex operations, ensuring accurate and efficient financial transactions.

## **Delta US Airline | Human Resource**

May 2022 - Aug 2022

 Administered health and life insurance benefits, as well as salary disbursements, for US airline employees.

#### **UK Car Insurance | Account Executive**

Oct 2020 - March 2022

 Handled car insurance quotation for UK clients, delivering comprehensive coverage solutions.

#### **CERTIFICATIONS**

## Information Technology Specialist in Networking | CERTIPORT

- · Networking Fundamentals and Infrastructures.
- Network Hardware, Protocols, and Services.
- · Network Troubleshooting.

## Network Security | CERTIPORT

- OS Security
- Network Device Security
- Secure Computing

#### **SKILLS**

Computer Programming UI/UX Designing Interpersonal and Communication Research Photography & Videography CRM, Canva, Figma, Adobe

#### **EDUCATION**

**Information and Communication Technology** 

University of Mindanao | 2018 - 2020

**Bachelor of Science in Information Technology** 

University of Mindanao | 2020 - Present